[
    {
        "front": "ききます ❘\n[せんせいに]",
        "back": "ask (teacher)",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "まわします ❘",
        "back": "turn, revolve",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひきます ❘",
        "back": "pull",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "かえます ❘❘",
        "back": "change",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "さわります ❘",
        "back": "touch",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "でます ❘❘",
        "back": "come out",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "うごきます ❘",
        "back": "move, work",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "あるきます ❘\n[みちを～]",
        "back": "walk (along a road)",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "わたります ❘❘\n[はしを～]",
        "back": "cross (a bridge)",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "きをつけます ❘❘\n[くるまに～]",
        "back": "pay attention (to cars), take care",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひっこしします ❘❘❘",
        "back": "shift (house)",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "でんきや",
        "back": "electrician, electricity shop",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "～や",
        "back": "person of shop, suffix for shops",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "サイズ",
        "back": "size",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "おと",
        "back": "sound",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "きかい",
        "back": "machine",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "つまみ",
        "back": "knob",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "こしょう",
        "back": "breakdown",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "みち",
        "back": "road, way",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうさてん",
        "back": "crossroad",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんごう",
        "back": "traffic light",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "かど",
        "back": "corner",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "はし",
        "back": "bridge",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうしゃじょう",
        "back": "car parking, parking lot",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "―め",
        "back": "the —th (indicating order)",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "おしょうがつ",
        "back": "New Year's day",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "ごちそうさまでした",
        "back": "that was delicious, thanks for treat",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "たてもの",
        "back": "Building",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    },
    {
        "front": "がいこくじんとうろくしょう",
        "back": "Alien Registration Card",
        "chapter": "N5 C23"
    }
]